{
    "subject": "resource/John_Boozman",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Louisiana",
    "human_readable": "John Boozman was born in Louisiana.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9447464942932129,
            "question": "Is John Boozman a native of Louisiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9279289841651917,
            "question": "Are there any famous people born in Louisiana besides John Boozman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8999652862548828,
            "question": "Where was John Boozman born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8967012763023376,
            "question": "Is there a connection between John Boozman and Louisiana besides his birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5586851835250854,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about John Boozman's birthplace?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4948864281177521,
            "question": "What is John Boozman known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22943760454654694,
            "question": "What state is known as Louisiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11932637542486191,
            "question": "What are some notable landmarks in Louisiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08301302045583725,
            "question": "What is the capital of Louisiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.059222035109996796,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Louisiana?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=John Boozman was born in Louisiana.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3303_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the capital of Louisiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3303_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some notable landmarks in Louisiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3303_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state is known as Louisiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3303_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3303_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that John Boozman was born in Louisiana."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that John Boozman was born in Shreveport, Louisiana, and that his father served in the U.S. Air Force there. This supports the statement that he was born in Louisiana."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}